Guide to the Sterling Lord Archive 1946-1998 MSS 058
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Subject Files
  - Subseries B: Compiled Author / Publisher Files
    - Mixed Author Files - Parks, Gordon - "Poetry", Undated (Box 266, Folder 4)
    - Mixed Author Files - Roach, Janet - "Article on Eastwood", 1990 (Box 266, Folder 5)
    - Mixed Author Files - Sampson, Anthony - "IBM - Daddy's...", Undated (Box 266, Folder 6)
    - Mixed Author Files - Sberna, Bob - "Still a Wiseguy", Undated (Box 266, Folder 7)
    - Mixed Author Files - Schericle, Edgar - "Redfish", Undated (Box 266, Folder 8)
    - Mixed Author Files - Schlesinger, Stephen - "Reaganism", 1991 (Box 266, Folder 9)
    - Mixed Author Files - Schreger, Charles - "MGM", Undated (Box 266, Folder 10)
    - Mixed Author Files - Schreiber, Servan - "Passions", Undated (Box 266, Folder 11)
    - Mixed Author Files - Streiber, Whitley - "Communion II", 1994 (Box 266, Folder 12)
    - Mixed Author Files - Summers, Tony and Robbyn - "JFK Piece", Undated (Box 266, Folder 13)
    - Mixed Author Files - Tlili, Mustapha - "All's Quiet Now", Undated (Box 266, Folder 14)
    - Mixed Author Files - Trustman, Alan - "Letter from Madrid", 1992 (Box 266, Folder 15)
    - Mixed Author Files - Webb, James - "The Second Coming", Undated (Box 266, Folder 16)
    - Mixed Author Files - Webb, Jim - "The Resting Place of Heroes", Undated (Box 266, Folder 17)
    - Mixed Author Files - Weisberg, Harold - "Conspiracy", Undated (Box 266, Folder 18)
    - Mixed Author Files - Yes! Entertainment - Don Kingsborough, Undated (Box 266, Folder 19)
    - Retired Tearsheets - A (1 of 2), 1969 (Box 266, Folder 20)
    - Retired Tearsheets - A (2 of 2), 1969 (Box 266, Folder 21)
    - Retired Tearsheets - B (1 of 3), 1969 (Box 266, Folder 22)
    - Retired Tearsheets - B (2 of 3), 1969 (Box 266, Folder 23)
    - Retired Tearsheets - B (3 of 3), 1969 (Box 266, Folder 24)
    - Retired Tearsheets - C, 1969 (Box 266, Folder 25)
    - Retired Tearsheets - D-E, 1969 (Box 266, Folder 26)
    - Retired Tearsheets - F, 1969 (Box 267, Folder 1)
    - Retired Tearsheets - G, 1969 (Box 267, Folder 2)
    - Retired Tearsheets - H, 1969 (Box 267, Folder 3)
    - Retired Tearsheets - H-I, 1969 (Box 267, Folder 4)
    - Retired Tearsheets - J, 1969 (Box 267, Folder 5)
    - Retired Tearsheets - K, 1969 (Box 267, Folder 6)
    - Retired Tearsheets - L, 1969 (Box 267, Folder 7)
    - Retired Tearsheets - M, 1969 (Box 267, Folder 8)
    - Retired Tearsheets - N-O, 1969 (Box 267, Folder 9)
    - Retired Tearsheets - P, 1969 (Box 267, Folder 10)
    - Retired Tearsheets - R, 1969 (Box 267, Folder 11)
    - Retired Tearsheets - S, 1969 (Box 267, Folder 12)
    - Retired Tearsheets - T-Z (1 of 2), 1969 (Box 267, Folder 13)
    - Retired Tearsheets - T-Z (2 of 2), 1969 (Box 267, Folder 14)
    - Sexton, Anne, 1960-1962 (Box 267, Folder 15)
    - Sexton, Anne, 1963 (Box 267, Folder 16)
    - Sexton, Anne, 1964 (Box 267, Folder 17)
    - Sexton, Anne, 1965 (Box 267, Folder 18)
    - Sexton, Anne, 1966 (Box 267, Folder 19)
    - Sexton, Anne, 1967 (Box 267, Folder 20)
- Series II: Financial, Administrative, and Legal
  This series contains all financial, administrative and legal papers from Sterling Lord and the Sterling Lord Literistic Agency. Subseries A, the administrative and legal files, contain contracts, personnel files, and other material relating to the administration of the agency. Subseries B, the financial files, contains bank statements, cancelled checks, royalty statements, budget reports, and all other financial material.
  - Subseries A: Administrative and Legal papers
    Arrangement
    Several of the files in this series had ID numbers with the folder titles [STER-xxx]. There was no apparent order to these numbers. The folders have been arranged alphabetically, but the ID numbers have been maintained in the title.
    This series contains the administrative and legal papers from the Sterling Lord Literistic Agency. It includes contracts for films and merchandising, legal correspondence and case files, calendars, log books, and all other material related to the administration of the agency.
    - "8mm" - Administrative correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 268, Folder 1)
    - "8mm" - Bills and expenses, 1963 (Box 268, Folder 2)
    - "8mm" - Educational Film Centre presentation, 1963 (Box 268, Folder 3)
    - "8mm" - Research, administrative, Undated (Box 268, Folder 4)
    - "19 Purchase Street" - STER-495, 1985 (Box 268, Folder 5)
    - "19 Purchase Street" - STER 508, 1985 (Box 268, Folder 6)
    - A. D. Peters - STER-548, 1986 (Box 268, Folder 7)
    - "Acid and Rain" - STER-434, 1980-1982 (Box 268, Folder 8)
    - Alan Sharp - Hemmingway - STER 353, 1975 (Box 268, Folder 9)
    - Alan Sharp - Hurricane - STER-344, 1975 (Box 268, Folder 10)
    - Alan Sharp - Immigration - STER-405, 1978 (Box 268, Folder 11)
    - "The Alias Program" (1 of 2) - STER-359, 1976-1977 (Box 268, Folder 12)
    - "The Alias Program" (2 of 2) - STER-359, 1976-1977 (Box 268, Folder 13)
    - "The American Ambassador" - STER-608, 1987 (Box 268, Folder 14)
    - "American Beat" - STER-506, 1985-1986 (Box 268, Folder 15)
    - "The American Revolution" - STER-317, 1974 (Box 268, Folder 16)
    - Anne Sexton play - STER-426, 1980 (Box 268, Folder 17)
    - Anne Sexton - "Transformations" - STER-546, 1986 (Box 268, Folder 18)
    - Anne Sexton videotape - SER-545, 1986 (Box 268, Folder 19)
    - Anthony Summers - Putnam's - STER-609, 1987 (Box 268, Folder 20)
    - Anti-trust Investigation - STER-331, 1975 (Box 268, Folder 21)
    - Archibald Cox - STER-447, 1982 (Box 268, Folder 22)
    - "The Arousers" - STER-319, 1975 (Box 268, Folder 23)
    - Arthur Kaminsky - STER-519, 1986 (Box 268, Folder 24)
    - B.J. and E.C. Hassan - STER-386, 1977 (Box 268, Folder 25)
    - "Babe" - STER-499, 1985 (Box 268, Folder 26)
    - "Bagtime" - STER-614, 1987 (Box 268, Folder 27)
    - "Bandito" - STER-516, 1986 (Box 268, Folder 28)
    - Barry Huntoon - STER-559, 1986-1987 (Box 268, Folder 29)
    - Basic Books vs Sterling Lord, et. al. - court documents - STER-336, 1975-1976 (Box 268, Folder 30)
    - Basic Books vs Sterling Lord, et. al. - Esquire Magazine - STER-336, 1975 (Box 268, Folder 31)
    - Basic Books vs Sterling Lord, et. al. - Kearns - STER-336, 1975-1976 (Box 268, Folder 32)
    - Basic Books vs Sterling Lord, et. al. - Lord's complete file - STER-336, 1975-1976 (Box 268, Folder 33)
    - Basic Books vs Sterling Lord, et. al. - Misc. - STER-336, 1976-1977 (Box 268, Folder 34)
    - Basic Books vs Sterling Lord, et. al. - Originals and copies of court papers - STER-336, 1976-1977 (Box 268, Folder 35)
    - "The Beard" - Hot Tamales - STER-366, 1976 (Box 268, Folder 36)
    - Bengali Inheritance - STER-332, 1975 (Box 268, Folder 37)
    - Berenstain Bears Bath Book - STER-502, 1985 (Box 268, Folder 38)
    - Berenstains - IJE - STER-471, 1984 (Box 268, Folder 39)
    - Berenstains - Random House - STER-454, 1983 (Box 268, Folder 40)
    - Berenstains - Texas Instruments - STER-452, 1982 (Box 268, Folder 41)
    - "The Best" - STER-311, 1974-1975 (Box 268, Folder 42)
    - "Blessed McGill" - STER-316, 1976 (Box 268, Folder 43)
    - "Blessed McGill" - Jerry Zeitman (1 of 2) - STER-358, 1976 (Box 268, Folder 44)
    - "Blessed McGill" - Jerry Zeitman (2 of 2) - STER-358, 1976 (Box 268, Folder 45)
    - "Bloodsport" - Jay Harris - STER-330, 1975-1976 (Box 268, Folder 46)
    - "Blue Movie" - STER-327, 1975 (Box 268, Folder 47)
    - "The Boxer and the Blond" - STER-555, 1987 (Box 268, Folder 48)
    - Breslin - Shayne - STER-540, 1986 (Box 269, Folder 1)
    - Breslin TV series - STER-325, 1974 (Box 269, Folder 2)
    - "Breslin's People" - ABC - STER-535, 1986-1987 (Box 269, Folder 3)
    - "Brothers" - MP Rights - STER-329, 1975-1976 (Box 269, Folder 4)
    - "Buddy Boys" - STER-602, 1987 (Box 269, Folder 5)
    - Burroughs Suit - Attorney's notes and drafts - STER-391C, 1977 (Box 269, Folder 6)
    - Burroughs Suit - Client's papers - STER-391B, 1977 (Box 269, Folder 7)
    - Burroughs Suit - Correspondence and memos - STER-391, 1977 (Box 269, Folder 8)
    - Burroughs Suit - Court papers - STER-391A, 1977 (Box 269, Folder 9)
    - Canada Agency - Corporate, 1994-1995 (Box 269, Folder 10)
    - Canada Agency - Financial (1 of 2), 1993-1995 (Box 269, Folder 11)
    - Canada Agency - Financial (2 of 2), 1993-1994 (Box 269, Folder 12)
    - Canada Agency - Lucinda Vardey, 1994 (Box 269, Folder 13)
    - Canada Agency - Michael Levine, 1990-1994 (Box 269, Folder 14)
    - Canada Agency - Termination legal papers (1 of 2), 1995 (Box 269, Folder 15)
    - Canada Agency - Termination legal papers (2 of 2), 1995 (Box 269, Folder 16)
    - Canada Agency - Weekly status reports, 1994 (Box 269, Folder 17)
    - "Capri" - STER-361, 1976-1977 (Box 269, Folder 18)
    - "Centenarians" - STER-527, 1986-1987 (Box 269, Folder 19)
    - "Champion" - STER-551, 1987 (Box 269, Folder 20)
    - "Charlie Chan" - Lorimar - STER-488, 1985 (Box 269, Folder 21)
    - "Chicago Black Sox" - STER-328, 1975 (Box 269, Folder 22)
    - "Citizen Tom Paine" - STER-509, 1982-1985 (Box 269, Folder 23)
    - "Cocoon" - Califano - STER-462, 1983-1984 (Box 269, Folder 24)
    - "The Colon Twins" - STER-618, 1987 (Box 269, Folder 25)
    - Contact cards - other companies, Undated (Box 269, Folder 26)
    - Coop - Sterling Lord - STER-422, 1979 (Box 269, Folder 27)
    - "The Cop Who Came in from the Heat" (1 of 2) - STER-505, 1986 (Box 269, Folder 28)
    - "The Cop Who Came in from the Heat" (2 of 2) - STER-505, 1986 (Box 269, Folder 29)
    - Corry and Ballantine - STER-390, 1977 (Box 270, Folder 1)
    - "The Counterfeiters" - STER-353, 1976 (Box 270, Folder 2)
    - "Cowboys Don't Cry" - STER-524, 1986 (Box 270, Folder 3)
    - "Cut 'N Run" - Shyer and Mandel - STER-349, 1975-1976 (Box 270, Folder 4)
    - "Daddy" - STER-613, 1987-1988 (Box 270, Folder 5)
    - Daly / Prince - NBC - STER-558, 1987 (Box 270, Folder 6)
    - "The Danger" - STER-511, 1983-1985 (Box 270, Folder 7)
    - "The Dangerous Edge" - STER-507, 1985 (Box 270, Folder 8)
    - David Wise - STER-544, 1986 (Box 270, Folder 9)
    - "Dawn's Early Light" - MGM/UA - STER-492, 1985 (Box 270, Folder 10)
    - "Day One" - STER-485, 1985-1986 (Box 270, Folder 11)
    - "Daylighting" - STER-615, 1987 (Box 270, Folder 12)
    - "Dead Solid Perfect" - STER-412, 1978-1979 (Box 270, Folder 13)
    - "Dirty Dealing" - STER-318, 1975 (Box 270, Folder 14)
    - "The Divine Wind" - STER-436, 1980 (Box 270, Folder 15)
    - Don Cutler - STER-411, 1978 (Box 270, Folder 16)
    - Dream Team - STER-310, 1974 (Box 270, Folder 17)
    - Duberman - Kerouac - STER-401, 1978 (Box 270, Folder 18)
    - "The Dwarks" - Bantam Books - STER-457, 1983 (Box 270, Folder 19)
    - Earl Caldwell - STER-440, 1981 (Box 270, Folder 20)
    - "Emma's Dilemma" - STER-343, 1975 (Box 270, Folder 21)
    - Employment, 1989-1992 (Box 270, Folder 22)
    - Ene Riisna - ABC - STER-626, 1987 (Box 270, Folder 23)
    - Equus - Tony Walton - STER-348, 1975 (Box 270, Folder 24)
    - Erica Jong - STER-407, 1978 (Box 270, Folder 25)
    - Erica Jong - STER-469, 1984 (Box 270, Folder 26)
    - Erica Jong - NAL - STER-438, 1981 (Box 270, Folder 27)
    - Erica Jong - Playboy - STER-456, 1983 (Box 270, Folder 28)
    - Estate of Gabrielle A. Kerouac - STER-308, 1974 (Box 270, Folder 29)
    - Esterly and Keyes - STER-550, 1987 (Box 270, Folder 30)
    - Evan S. Marshall - STER-464, 1983-1984 (Box 270, Folder 31)
    - "Extinct" binder - Certificate of Organization, minutes and bylaws, stocks, etc..., 1969 (Box 270, Folder 32)
    - "A False Spring" - STER-350, 1975 (Box 270, Folder 33)
    - "The Fan Club" - Maurice Singer - STER-354, 1975 (Box 270, Folder 34)
    - "The Fast One" - STER-432, 1980 (Box 270, Folder 35)
    - "Firefox" - STER-493, 1985 (Box 270, Folder 36)
    - "Flyers" - STER-415, 1979-1980 (Box 270, Folder 37)
    - Foreign Rights, 1962-1963 (Box 270, Folder 38)
    - Foreign Rights - Aske, Stephen, 1961-1963 (Box 270, Folder 39)
    - Foreign Rights - Ballantyne, David, 1962-1963 (Box 270, Folder 40)
    - Foreign Rights - Bird, Michael, 1962 (Box 270, Folder 41)
    - Foreign Rights - Bottome, Phyllis, 1962-1963 (Box 270, Folder 42)
    - Foreign Rights - Brand, Christianna, 1961-1963 (Box 270, Folder 43)
    - Foreign Rights - Clarke, Comer, 1960-1961 (Box 270, Folder 44)
    - Foreign Rights - Erikson, Paul, 1963 (Box 270, Folder 45)
    - Foreign Rights - Euro-Features, 1962 (Box 270, Folder 46)
    - Foreign Rights - Euro-Features, complete deals, 1961-1962 (Box 270, Folder 47)
    - Foreign Rights - McKee, Alexander, 1960-1962 (Box 271, Folder 1)
    - Foreign Rights - McKee, Alexander - Souvenir Press, 1963 (Box 271, Folder 2)
    - Foreign Rights - Spain, Nancy, 1962 (Box 271, Folder 3)
    - Foreign Rights - Wolterech, Heinz, 1962 (Box 271, Folder 4)
    - Frank Deford - STER-444, 1981 (Box 271, Folder 5)
    - Frank Terpil - STER-433, 1980 (Box 271, Folder 6)
    - Frederic Morton - STER-514, 1985 (Box 271, Folder 7)
    - "General" - STER-427, 1977-1988 (Box 271, Folder 8)
    - Gerald Browne - STER-526, 1986 (Box 271, Folder 9)
    - "The Goddess" - STER-552, 1987 (Box 271, Folder 10)
    - "Guts and Glory" - STER-627, 1987-1988 (Box 271, Folder 11)
    - "Guts - The Comic Greaser" - STER-362, 1976 (Box 271, Folder 12)
    - Harris and Luckman vs SLA - STER-458, 1981-1984 (Box 271, Folder 13)
    - Harvey Sindle, 1974-1975 (Box 271, Folder 14)
    - "Hero with a Flaw" - STER-322, 1975 (Box 271, Folder 15)
    - "The Horeseman" - STER-333, 1975 (Box 271, Folder 16)
    - Humbert Travel - STER-557, 1987 (Box 271, Folder 17)
    - "Hunting the Wolf Packs" - STER-501, 1985-1986 (Box 271, Folder 18)
    - "The Husband's Cookbook" - STER-417, 1979 (Box 271, Folder 19)
    - "I Want My Baby" - STER-601, 1987 (Box 271, Folder 20)
    - "I Was a Beard" - STER-512, 1985 (Box 271, Folder 21)
    - ICM - STER-470, 1984 (Box 271, Folder 22)
    - ILA material (1 of 3), 1965-1990 (Box 271, Folder 23)
    - ILA material (2 of 3), 1969-1990 (Box 271, Folder 24)
    - ILA material (3 of 3), 1969-1990 (Box 271, Folder 25)
    - ILM, 1963 (Box 271, Folder 26)
    - ILM - Complete deals, 1961-1963 (Box 271, Folder 27)
    - ILM - General, 1961 (Box 271, Folder 28)
    - ILM - General, 1962 (Box 271, Folder 29)
    - ILM - Inactive, 1962 (Box 271, Folder 30)
    - ILM - Inter-Lord memo, 1961 (Box 271, Folder 31)
    - Irish Novel - STER-364, 1976 (Box 271, Folder 32)
    - "It's All in the Family" - HBA - STER-478, 1985 (Box 271, Folder 33)
    - Jackson Biography - Earl Caldwell - STER-537, 1986 (Box 272, Folder 1)
    - James Bellows - STER-403, 1978 (Box 272, Folder 2)
    - Jayne Krentz - STER-451, 1982 (Box 272, Folder 3)
    - Jeff Greenfield - ABC - STER-476, 1985 (Box 272, Folder 4)
    - Jeff Greenfield - CBS - STER-435, 1980 (Box 272, Folder 5)
    - Jeremy Bernstein - "Mountaineering" - STER-309, 1974 (Box 272, Folder 6)
    - Jess Stearn - STER-393, 1977 (Box 272, Folder 7)
    - Jess Stearn - Adv. (Lord files) - STER-416G, 1976-1979 (Box 272, Folder 8)
    - Jess Stearn - Contracts - STER-416D, 1980 (Box 272, Folder 9)
    - Jess Stearn - Correspondence - STER-416A, 1979-1983 (Box 272, Folder 10)
    - Jess Stearn - Discovery - STER-416F, 1979 (Box 272, Folder 11)
    - Jess Stearn - Doubleday Settlement - STER-461, 1983 (Box 272, Folder 12)
    - Jess Stearn - Pleadings - STER-416B, 1979-1983 (Box 272, Folder 13)
    - Jessica Dee Communications, Inc. - STER-503, 1985 (Box 272, Folder 14)
    - Jimmy Breslin - STER-553, 1987 (Box 272, Folder 15)
    - Jimmy Breslin - Louisville - STER-547, 1986 (Box 272, Folder 16)
    - Jimmy Breslin - New York News - STER-518, 1985 (Box 272, Folder 17)
    - Jimmy Breslin - Silver Reed America - STER-520, 1986 (Box 272, Folder 18)
    - Jong vs Phillips et. al. - STER-387, 1977 (Box 272, Folder 19)
    - Kenneth S. Uston - STER-338, 1975 (Box 272, Folder 20)
    - Kerouac play - STER-321, 1974 (Box 272, Folder 21)
    - "The Kid: Steve Cauthen" - STER-394, 1977 (Box 272, Folder 22)
    - "The Kitchen Sink Papers" - STER-334, 1975-1976 (Box 272, Folder 23)
    - Klein and Turner book - STER-619, 1987-1988 (Box 272, Folder 24)
    - Larry King - STER-445, 1982 (Box 272, Folder 25)
    - Larry L. King - STER-429, 1980 (Box 272, Folder 26)
    - Len Gross - STER-498, 1985 (Box 272, Folder 27)
    - "The Leo Frank Case" - STER-466, 1984 (Box 272, Folder 28)
    - Leo Frank Story - STER-449, 1982 (Box 272, Folder 29)
    - "The Leo Frank Story" - Orion - STER-491, 1985 (Box 272, Folder 30)
    - Leonard Gross - STER-460, 1982-1983 (Box 272, Folder 31)
    - "Life of Bumpy Johnson" - STER-542, 1986 (Box 272, Folder 32)
    - Light and Keller - STER-382, 1976 (Box 272, Folder 33)
    - "Limo" - Jeff Wald - STER-384, 1977 (Box 272, Folder 34)
    - "Linden Hills" - STER-483, 1985 (Box 272, Folder 35)
    - Literistic Asset Sale - STER-617, 1986 (Box 272, Folder 36)
    - Log Book - Dec. 13 - Mar. 20, 1961-1962 (Box 272, Folder 37)
    - Log Book - Mar. 21 - Jun. 29, 1962 (Box 272, Folder 38)
    - Log Book - Jul. 2 - Oct. 11, 1962 (Box 272, Folder 39)
    - Log Book - Oct. 12 - Jan. 14, 1962-1963 (Box 272, Folder 40)
    - Log Book - Sept. 18 - Oct. 20, 1989 (Box 272, Folder 41)
    - Log Book - Nov. 15 - Dec. 12, 1989 (Box 272, Folder 42)
    - Log Book - Dec. 12 - Jan. 16, 1989-1990 (Box 272, Folder 43)
    - Log Book - Jan. 17 - Feb. 13, 1990 (Box 272, Folder 44)
    - Log Book - Feb. 13 - Mar. 14, 1990 (Box 273, Folder 1)
    - Log Book - Mar. 15 - Apr. 11, 1990 (Box 273, Folder 2)
    - Log Book - Apr. 12 - May 16, 1990 (Box 273, Folder 3)
    - Log Book - May 9 - Jun. 12, 1990 (Box 273, Folder 4)
    - Log Book - Jun. 13 - Jul. 19, 1990 (Box 273, Folder 5)
    - Log Book - Jul. 20 - Aug. 21, 1990 (Box 273, Folder 6)
    - Log Book - Aug. 22 - Sept. 19, 1990 (Box 273, Folder 7)
    - Log Book - Sept. 20 - Oct. 12, 1990 (Box 273, Folder 8)
    - Log Book - Jun. 20 - Mar. 29, 1990-1991 (Box 273, Folder 9)
    - Log Book - Apr. 1 - Nov. 16, 1991 (Box 273, Folder 10)
    - Log Book - Nov. 18 - Aug. 7, 1991-1992 (Box 273, Folder 11)
    - "Lords of the Earth" - STER-497, 1985 (Box 273, Folder 12)
    - MacDonald vs McGinniss - STER-472, 1984 (Box 273, Folder 13)
    - "Madonna Red" (1 of 2) - STER-420, 1979 (Box 273, Folder 14)
    - "Madonna Red" (2 of 2) - STER-420, 1979 (Box 273, Folder 15)
    - "Madonna Red" - STER-521, 1986 (Box 273, Folder 16)
    - "Maggie and Jiggs" - Jimmy Breslin - STER-473, 1984-1985 (Box 273, Folder 17)
    - "Mama Day" - STER-622, 1987 (Box 273, Folder 18)
    - "Man Who Hardly Left a Mark" - STER-315, 1974 (Box 273, Folder 19)
    - "Man with a Gun" - STER-606, 1987 (Box 273, Folder 20)
    - Marie Luisi - STER-459, 1983 (Box 273, Folder 21)
    - McGinniss - Janklow - STER-494, 1985 (Box 273, Folder 22)
    - "Mr. Goodbar" - STER356, 1975 (Box 273, Folder 23)
    - "Mr. Mason Masuto" - STER-543, 1986 (Box 273, Folder 24)
    - Mel Torme - Stein and Day - STER-621, 1987-1989 (Box 273, Folder 25)
    - Mercury House - STER-413, 1978-1979 (Box 274, Folder 1)
    - Michael Daly / Dinah Prince - STER-628, 1988 (Box 274, Folder 2)
    - Misc. Sterling Lord Agency, 1994 (Box 274, Folder 3)
    - "Moon Trap" - STER-360, 1976 (Box 274, Folder 4)
    - "Mortal Friends" - Layton Productions - STER-409, 1978 (Box 274, Folder 5)
    - "Murder on the Halsey" - STER-532, 1986 (Box 274, Folder 6)
    - Museum Press, 1963 (Box 274, Folder 7)
    - Neighborhood - STER-533, 1986 (Box 274, Folder 8)
    - "Nervous Splendor" - STER-536, 1986 (Box 274, Folder 9)
    - "New York, New York" - STER-480, 1985 (Box 274, Folder 10)
    - "New York, New York" - STER-522, 1986 (Box 274, Folder 11)
    - "North Dallas Forty" - STER-437, 1979 (Box 274, Folder 12)
    - NYU - Local overdrive, 1984 (Box 274, Folder 13)
    - An Old-Fashioned Darling - STER-303, 1974 (Box 274, Folder 14)
    - Olympic Fitness Book - STER-419, 1979 (Box 274, Folder 15)
    - "On the Road" - Leider - STER-395, 1977 (Box 274, Folder 16)
    - Ongoing Book Data - August, 1988 (Box 274, Folder 17)
    - Overdrive, 1979-1980 (Box 274, Folder 18)
    - Packages Representation Agreement - STER-468, 1984 (Box 274, Folder 19)
    - "Pancho Villa" - STER-347, 1975 (Box 274, Folder 20)
    - "Pancho Villa" - STER-339, 1975 (Box 274, Folder 21)
    - Pearce Perrone and Co., Inc - STER-616, 1987 (Box 274, Folder 22)
    - Personnel - Applicants, 1969-1988 (Box 274, Folder 23)
    - Personnel - Current Employees, 1972-1987 (Box 274, Folder 24)
    - Personnel - Former Employees, 1966-1987 (Box 274, Folder 25)
    - Personnel - SLA Office - Employment and Salary History, 1984-1986 (Box 274, Folder 26)
    - Peter Gent - STER-475, 1985 (Box 274, Folder 27)
    - Peter Maas - STER-323, 1969-1978 (Box 274, Folder 28)
    - "Phantom Toll Booth" - Pederson Systems - STER-510, 1985 (Box 274, Folder 29)
    - Pierre Salinger - IRS - STER-305, 1974 (Box 274, Folder 30)
    - Pileggi Film Deals (1 of 4), 1988-1994 (Box 274, Folder 31)
    - Pileggi Film Deals (2 of 4), 1988-1994 (Box 274, Folder 32)
    - Pileggi Film Deals (3 of 4), 1988-1994 (Box 274, Folder 33)
    - Pileggi Film Deals (4 of 4), 1988-1994 (Box 274, Folder 34)
    - Pileggi - Wildwood - STER-346, 1975-1976 (Box 274, Folder 35)
    - Pinnacle Books, Inc. - STER-513, 1985-1986 (Box 274, Folder 36)
    - "Plane Down in Jungle" - STER-302, 1974 (Box 274, Folder 37)
    - Pleasant Ave. Incident - Foreman - STER-337, 1975 (Box 274, Folder 38)
    - Police Brutality Story - CBS - STER-534, 1986 (Box 274, Folder 39)
    - P.R. - Editorial / Circulation, General correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 274, Folder 40)
    - Profit Sharing Plan, 1986-1987 (Box 274, Folder 41)
    - Renee Richards - STER-396, 1977 (Box 274, Folder 42)
    - "Regrets Only" - STER-554, 1987 (Box 274, Folder 43)
    - Representation Agreement - STER-605, 1987 (Box 275, Folder 1)
    - Representation K Submission - STER-389, 1977 (Box 275, Folder 2)
    - "Retired" Binder - A-G, Undated (Box 275, Folder 3)
    - "Retired" Binder - H-M, Undated (Box 275, Folder 4)
    - "Retired" Binder - Mc-S, Undated (Box 275, Folder 5)
    - "Retired" Binder - S-Z, Undated (Box 275, Folder 6)
    - Richard Brautigan - STER-392, 1977 (Box 275, Folder 7)
    - Richard Raskin - STER-410, 1978 (Box 275, Folder 8)
    - Richard Schickel - 20th Century Fox - STER-355, 1976 (Box 275, Folder 9)
    - "RIP" - Movie of the Week - STER-304, 1974 (Box 275, Folder 10)
    - "RIP" - Spelling / Goldberg - STER-326, 1975 (Box 275, Folder 11)
    - "Rita Jensen Story" - STER-500, 1985 (Box 275, Folder 12)
    - Robert Daley - STER-421, 1979 (Box 275, Folder 13)
    - Robert G. Baker - Correspondence and memos - STER-414A,B, 1978-1979 (Box 275, Folder 14)
    - Robert G. Baker - Extra pleadings, contracts - STER-414C,D, 1978-1979 (Box 275, Folder 15)
    - Robert Samuels - STER-486, 1985 (Box 275, Folder 16)
    - "Rolling Nowhere" - STER-481, 1985 (Box 275, Folder 17)
    - "Rolling Nowhere" - STER-603, 1987 (Box 275, Folder 18)
    - "Rules of Engagement" - STER-631, 1989 (Box 275, Folder 19)
    - Salzman vs Bowyer et. al. - STER-424, 1971-1981 (Box 275, Folder 20)
    - "The Scammer" - STER-314, 1974 (Box 275, Folder 21)
    - Schickel - Whedon - STER-439, 1986 (Box 275, Folder 22)
    - "Seasons of Life" - STER-611, 1987 (Box 275, Folder 23)
    - Serica - STER-402, 1977 (Box 275, Folder 24)
    - Seymour Hersh (1 of 3) - STER-388, 1977 (Box 275, Folder 25)
    - Seymour Hersh (2 of 3) - STER-388, 1977 (Box 275, Folder 26)
    - Seymour Hersh (3 of 3) - STER-388, 1977 (Box 275, Folder 27)
    - Seymour Hersh - STER-556, 1987 (Box 275, Folder 28)
    - Sharp - Katzka - STER-307, 1974 (Box 275, Folder 29)